let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which is used to find and fix bugs in the Java programs.?",
        answer: "JDB",
        options: [
            "JVM",
            "JDB",
            "JDK",
            "JRE",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What is the return type of the hashCode() method in the Object class?",
        answer: "int",
        options: ["int", "object", "long", "void"],
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which package contains the Random class?",
        answer: "java.util package",
        options: [
            "java.util package",
            "java.lang package",
            "java.awt package",
            "java.io package",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "An interface with no fields or methods is known as?",
        answer: "Marker Interface",
        options: [
            "Runnable Interface",
            "Abstract Interface",
            "Marker Interface",
            "charSequence Interface"
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "In which memory a String is stored, when we create a string using new operator?",
        answer: "Heap memory",
        options: ["Stack", "String memory", "Random storage space",
            "Heap memory"],
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which of the following is a marker interface?",
        answer: "Remote interface",
        options: ["Runnable interface",
            "Remote interface",
            "Readable interfac",
            "Result interface"],
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which keyword is used for accessing the features of a package?",
        answer: "import",
        options: ["import",
            "package",
            "extends",
            "export"],
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "In java, jar stands for?",
        answer: "Java Archive",
        options: ["Java Archive Runner",
            "Java Archive",
            "Java Application Resource",
            "Java Application Runner"],
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which of the following is a mutable class in java?",
        answer: "java.lang.StringBuilder",
        options: ["java.lang.StringBuilder",
            "java.lang.Short",
            "java.lang.Byte",
            "java.lang.String"],
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which of the following option leads to the portability and security of Java?",
        answer: "Bytecode is executed by JVM",
        options: ["Bytecode is executed by JVM",
            "The applet makes the Java code secure and portable",
            "Use of exception handling",
            "Dynamic binding between objects"],
    }
];